<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[RUA Architects & Designers]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[RUA Architects & Designers]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/rua-architects-designers/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:56:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/rua-architects-designers/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Story so far....]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Story so far....</h1><p>We are advocates, educationalists, environmentalists, researchers, designers and architects. We create spaces that impact and fundamentally change the way people work and experience. We believe that good design is good business and that it should not cost the earth. We are a bespoke design practice that collaborates with larger practice to bring a unique brand of innovation in Interiors Practice resulting in award winning responsive and effective interior architecture. We support multi disciplinary design team proposals with the strongest individual CVs in the Irish Market. With large commercial interiors practice experience in Healthcare, Education, Public Space, Hospitality, Workspace, we add significant weight to competitive proposals. The RUA Team has over 25 National and International Awards and carries with them an international profile. We are Registered Architects and Certified Passive House Designers. We take on selective private residential projects that share our aspiration for a high quality of design and the highest environmental passive standards. Contact us to propose a collaboration or for a specific project </p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/a1eaa4c391144222ccf69afa95dba4b8/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=3745&cropwidth=5616&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fd8f92dca-acb7-46e2-8a05-20ac0552cbc4.jpg&x=0&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d8f92dca-acb7-46e2-8a05-20ac0552cbc4.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e6ddf7e6-7f62-4efd-a560-a9919663a134</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:55:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating memorable Spaces]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Creating memorable Spaces</h1><p>RUA Architects have been creating memorable responsive buildings and spaces for 20 years. Their work is innovative, sustainable, award winning and entirely different to other practices. They seek to push the boundaries of the mundane to excite, enthuse and elate. Their interiors and architecture have been celebrated worldwide at awards and exhibitions from here in Ireland to Italy, Singapore, China and the US.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/20393c35f2a9a89406a3391f506971ec/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=590&cropwidth=1417&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Ff1eb5f3c-acb2-4ba4-8907-c0a4fabf826d.jpg&x=0&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f1eb5f3c-acb2-4ba4-8907-c0a4fabf826d.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee04ae5a-0a28-47b4-8e13-d309bcf86135</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Four + Marvel Collection]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Five Four + Marvel Collection</h1><p>Some comic book apparel can end up juvenile, but the new Five Four collaboration with Marvel is anything but. In celebration of the impending release of Avengers: Age of Ultron, the Five Four subscription menswear service finds subtlety in the generally loud graphic medium by using Marvel's famous roster of superheroes to inspire its April capsule.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c00f82bc7a96b03780b683692320bb03f3b031f2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/style/five-four-marvel-collection</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">adcc567a-3a7e-4873-9cf2-020847ceda96</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:36:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mido Eyewear Show 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Mido Eyewear Show 2016</h1><p>While you might not have heard of it, Italy's Mido Eyewear Show is the leading event for eyewear professionals. It's an exhibition during which major international brands present their new styles and innovations for prescription specs and sunglasses-and, while it might sound like it's purely for industry members, it's fascinating for anybody interested in fashion and design.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e0e4e7f9c24bc25e24721945becf5f7aec28e9a0.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/design/mido-eyewear-show-preview-milan</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e8126e1e-34b1-43d4-b669-7c007559cbe0</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:36:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design Indaba 2016: Interview With Jaime Hayon]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Design Indaba 2016: Interview With Jaime Hayon</h1><p>It's four o'clock in the morning and Jaime Hayon is still going full speed, sitting on a couch in Cape Town, candidly telling us about the time he tattooed one of the world's top tattoo artists. Had he ever inked somebody before? Nope, and he never did again.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/48f86a6be147d551b27ad334ff404c5fb1ce9b36.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/design/interview-designer-jaime-haydon-design-indaba</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c2651fc2-7540-4354-b132-3f676772984b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:36:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>