<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[RUA Architects & Designers]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[RUA Architects & Designers]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/rua-architects-designers/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 18:22:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/rua-architects-designers/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating memorable Spaces]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Creating memorable Spaces</h1><p>RUA Architects have been creating memorable responsive buildings and spaces for 20 years. Their work is innovative, sustainable, award winning and entirely different to other practices. They seek to push the boundaries of the mundane to excite, enthuse and elate. Their interiors and architecture have been celebrated worldwide at awards and exhibitions from here in Ireland to Italy, Singapore, China and the US.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/bcbf05b1449c39289e26b735b71db1ae/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=589&cropwidth=1417&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fs3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fthe-grid-img%2Fp%2Fa7b79ef23a641b37aa90610d126e9f91defe6311.jpg&x=0&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f1eb5f3c-acb2-4ba4-8907-c0a4fabf826d.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee04ae5a-0a28-47b4-8e13-d309bcf86135</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 18:19:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Story so far....]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Story so far....</h1><p>We are advocates, educationalists, environmentalists, researchers, designers and architects. We create spaces that impact and fundamentally change the way people work and experience. We believe that good design is good business and that it should not cost the earth. We are a bespoke design practice that collaborates with larger practice to bring a unique brand of innovation in Interiors Practice resulting in award winning responsive and effective interior architecture. We support multi disciplinary design team proposals with the strongest individual CVs in the Irish Market. With large commercial interiors practice experience in Healthcare, Education, Public Space, Hospitality, Workspace, we add significant weight to competitive proposals. The RUA Team has over 25 National and International Awards and carries with them an international profile. We are Registered Architects and Certified Passive House Designers. We take on selective private residential projects that share our aspiration for a high quality of design and the highest environmental passive standards. Contact us to propose a collaboration or for a specific project</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/497cc562a6afb26133e4eb75e26d70c06d2a4bf4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d8f92dca-acb7-46e2-8a05-20ac0552cbc4.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e6ddf7e6-7f62-4efd-a560-a9919663a134</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 18:18:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Talk with Marc O'Riain - Bloom]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A Talk with Marc O'Riain - Bloom</h1><p>Luzie (my creative partner in crime) and I popped over to the Design Hub to listen to one of Ireland's most senior awarded commercial interior architecture professionals to discuss his work on The Architecture Factory, a building part of the CIT campus.</p><img src="http://www.thisisbloom.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/marc-o-riain.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.thisisbloom.com/2015/11/03/a-talk-with-marc-oriain/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2c562a0e-0518-435b-acad-562201722e4d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 18:21:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marc O'Riain : IDI Awards Exhibition]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Marc O'Riain : IDI Awards Exhibition</h1><p>The IDI Awards Exhibition is in Waterford from the end of January in the SOMA Gallery from January 29th and running for a month. The IDI Irish Design awards feature the best of furniture, product, interiors, architecture, fashion, textiles, app, user experience, graphics and web design in Ireland.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/153773624</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c534aa9a-3975-4941-8db1-d1d12ade10f0</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 18:14:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[fuse:d launch night]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>fuse:d launch night</h1><p>Marc talking Design in WaterfordJuly 4, 2016Marc was delighted to talk at the inaugural Fuse:d design network in Waterford. Below is the full talk on the future for design in Ireland.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/5ff24d28105a3a4dd653e9d8e37ab301/noop.jpg?input=http%3A%2F%2Fimg.youtube.com%2Fvi%2FBEC1yVT2ePI%2Fmaxresdefault.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/BEC1yVT2ePI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">71a021ef-d0a0-417d-96e7-9c35cc480860</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 18:11:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>